Here with Broncos assistant GM Reed
Burkhardt, just selected Tyler Onyedum
with the 66th overall pick, traded back
from 62. After trading back, what's it
like in that war room as you're waiting
to see if Tyler's still going to be on
the board? Well, we're working the
phones a lot. We're you know, we're
trying to get the best value possible
and and we're mindful of not losing
Tyler. And so
finding that happy medium of getting
value, getting the extra pick that we
got from Buffalo and and still getting
our target. Absolutely. And and with
Tyler, what stands out about him? What
should Broncos country know about him as
a player? He's a heavy-handed run
defender. He can also rush the passer. I
think most importantly is his wiring,
his makeup. It's a perfect fit for Vance
in his defense and Jamar in that room
and
we're excited to get him going. Reed,
we've seen this team over the last two
or three seasons really build at the
line of scrimmage, offensive line,
defensive line, win up front. How much
of continuing that sort of mentality was
went into this pick? It's the backbone
of our team, not only the defensive
line, but the offensive line. And when
you get a chance to add a player of his
caliber to our defensive line and and
see what Vance can do with those guys,
what Jamar can do with those guys, it's
only going to make us better. Reed,
thanks for your time. Good luck the rest
of the way. Thank you.